AHMED OMAR EL DEEB

16 St El Lethe Hassan Mohamed El Haram, Giza. • +20122 702 4718 • ahmedomar031@gmail.com

http://aeldeeb.com/

OBJECTIVE

Obtaining a web development position that enables me to learn new technologies while utilizing my experience in developing web-based applications. I'm dependable and willing to develop my skills to join a professional work environment.

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Fresh Graduate with 1 year experience in web development. With special interest in open source technologies like Linux, Apache, MySQL & PHP [LAMP]

• Programming Languages: PHP, Javascript, Visual Basic, Jquery, Ajax

Markup Languages: HTML, CSS Database: MySQL, MS SQL Source Control: SVN, GIT PHP Frameworks: Codeigniter

• PHP CMS : Drupal

• Image Manipulation Programs: Gimp, Adobe Photoshop

Operating Systems: Linux (Ubuntu), Windows

WORK EXPERIENCE

Damlag, Zamalek, Cairo, Egypt Junior Web Developer

nov 2011 to present

- http://www.zamalekartgallery.com/
 - http://www.elcinema.com/
 - http://misrinternationalfilms.com/
 - http://oscargroupeg.net/

Tqniat, Madie, Cairo, Egypt Junior Web Developer

Apr 2011 to may 2011

- http://www.kwikkopyegypt.com/
- http://www.premieregypt.com
- http://www.tqniat.com/
- perfect horizon

Damlag, Smart Village, Cairo, Egypt Junior Web Developer

March 2010 to June 2010

- http://www.elcinema.com/
- http://3d.elcinema.com/

EDUCATION

B.S. Faculty of Commerce, Alexandria University

Jan 2010 (ongoing)

Specialized in Business Administration Expected to graduate in June 2014

COURSES

- Elementary level & general English program (British Council)
- Object Oriented Programming Concepts (YAT)
- SQL server 2005 core (YAT)
- Visual basic 2005 core (YAT)

.Net Framework 3.0 (YAT)

LANGUAGES

Arabic: Native language

English: Good

ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS

Computers, going to the Gym, swimming, watching movies.

REFERENCES

Available upon request